what is the area and perimeter of this
rectangle there is going to be base
times height so we can just say a equals
then the base is this right here times
the height which is this right here and
we can see that this is an A minus B
times an A plus b that is a difference
of two squares so it's just going to be
equal to a squared minus B squared or in
other words 105 squared minus 2 root
2739 squared 105 squared is 11 25 minus
and then 2 squared is 4 and root 2739
squared is 2739 and 1125 minus 10 956 is
69 nice and next let's find the
perimeter we're going to do 2 of this
side here plus 2 of this side here these
twos can distribute which would give us
210 minus 4 root two seven three nine
plus two ten plus four root two seven
three nine these two match but one's
positive one's negative so they cancel
each other out so we're just left with
the perimeter equal to 210 plus 210
which is 420. so the area is 69 and the
parameter is 420. nice